Finding Aid for Martha Wright Griffiths Papers 1956-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Congressional Papers 1955-1974
  - 90th Congress 1967-1968
    - Legislative files
      - Ways and Means (Box 28)
      - Ways and Means (Box 29)
    - Bills introduced by MWG (Box 29)
    - Topical Files
      - Aid to Dependent Children (Box 29)
      - Agriculture Dept., 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Anderson, Dr. Norma (Box 29)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 29)
      - Campaign 1968, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Carmichael, Stokely (Box 29)
      - Census and surveys (various) (Box 29)
      - Census (protesting questions to be asked in 1970) (Box 29)
      - Civil Rights
        - General (Box 29)
        - Opening housing (Box 29)
      - Colleagues (communications with) (Box 30)
      - Commerce Dept (Box 30)
      - Committee on Committees (Box 30)
      - Crime (Box 30)
      - Cuba (Box 30)
      - Defense Dept. (Box 30)
      - Democratic Convention (Box 30)
      - Democratic National Committee (Box 30)
      - Democratic (17th District Democratic Party (Box 30)
      - Detroit
        - General (Box 30)
        - Detroit Riot (Box 30)
      - Education (Box 30)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 30)
      - Executive Branch (Box 30)
      - Extremist groups (Box 30)
      - Federal Communications Commission (Box 30)
      - Federal Trade Commission (Box 30)
      - Food and Drug Administration (Box 30)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 30)
      - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission (Box 30)
      - Foreign Policy
        - General (Box 30)
        - Biafra (Box 30)
        - Middle East (Box 30)
        - Vietnam, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Government Operations (Box 30)
      - Government spending (Box 30)
      - Health, Education and Welfare Dept (Box 30)
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 31)
      - Interior Dept (Box 31)
      - Justice Dept (Box 31)
      - King, Martin Luther (Box 31)
      - Labor Dept (Box 31)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 31)
      - National Organization for Women (Box 31)
      - Newspaper strikes (Box 31)
      - Poverty Program (Box 31)
      - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box 31)
      - Public debt (Box 31)
      - Questionnaire (Box 31)
      - Statements of MWG (Box 31)
      - Subversive Activities Control Board (Box 31)
      - Supreme Court (Box 31)
      - Teachers' strike (Box 31)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 31)
      - Transportation Dept (Box 31)
      - Treasury Dept
        - General (Box 31)
        - Bureau of Customs (Box 31)
      - Wage-price controls (Box 31)
      - Women-Discrimination (Box 31)
  - 91st Congress 1969-1970
    - Legislative files
      - Agriculture (Box 31)
      - Appropriations (Box 31)
      - Armed Services (Box 32)
      - Banking and Currency (Box 32)
      - District of Columbia (Box 32)
      - Education and Labor (Box 32)
      - Foreign Affairs (Box 32)
      - Government Operations (Box 32)
      - House Administration (Box 32)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs (Box 32)
      - Internal Security (Box 32)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 32)
      - Judiciary (Box 32)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 32)
      - Post Office and Civil Service (Box 32)
      - Public Works (Box 33)
      - Rules (Box 33)
      - Science and Astronautics (Box 33)
      - Veterans Affairs (Box 33)
      - Ways and Means (Box 33)
      - Ways and Means (Box 34)
      - Joint Economic Committee
        - General (Box 34)
        - Subcommittee on Fiscal Policy (Box 34)
        - Subcommittee on Economy in Government (Box 34)
    - Bills introduced by MWG (Box 35)
    - Bills introduced by MWG (Box 36)
    - Topical Files
      - Abortion (Box 36)
      - Agency for International Development (Box 36)
      - Agnew, Spiro (Box 36)
      - Agriculture Dept (Box 36)
      - Aid to Dependent Children (Box 36)
      - Air and water pollution (Box 36)
      - Armaments (Box 36)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 36)
      - Automobile companies (Box 36)
      - Automobile safety (Box 36)
      - Blacks (Box 36)
      - Cabinet appointments (Box 36)
      - Census reform and surveys (Box 36)
      - Chalmers, Gladys (Box 36)
      - Chemical and poison gas (Box 36)
      - Civil Rights (Box 36)
      - Civil Service (Box 36)
      - Colleagues (communications with) (Box 36)
      - Commerce Dept
        - General (Box 36)
        - Smith, Gerald L.K (Box 36)
      - Committee on Committees (Box 36)
      - Congressional (declaration of war) (Box 36)
      - Congressional Record inserts (Box 36)
      - Consumer legislation (Box 36)
      - Corps of Engineers (Box 36)
      - Crime (Box 36)
      - Crockett, Judge George (Box 37)
      - Day-Care Centers (Box 37)
      - Daylight saving time (Box 37)
      - Defense Dept. (Box 37)
      - Democratic National Committee (Box 37)
      - Detroit
        - General (Box 37)
        - School redistricting (Box 37)
        - Schools (burning of flags, separatist flags) (Box 37)
      - Dow Chemical (Box 37)
      - Draft deferments (podiatry) (Box 37)
      - Drugs (Box 37)
      - Education (Box 37)
      - Election reforms (Box 37)
      - Environmental pollution (Box 37)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 37)
      - Executive Branch (Box 37)
      - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 37)
      - Federal Communications Commission
        - General (Box 37)
        - Pay-TV (Box 37)
      - Federal Home Loan Bank Board (Box 37)
      - Federal Housing Administration (Box 37)
      - Federal pay raises (Box 37)
      - Federal Reserve System (Box 37)
      - Federal Trade Commission (Box 37)
      - Food and Drug Administration (Box 37)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 37)
      - Foreign Policy
        - General (Box 37)
        - Biafra (Box 37)
        - Cambodia, 2 folders (Box 37)
        - Laos (Box 37)
        - Middle East (Box 37)
        - Pueblo seizure (Box 37)
        - Vietnam, 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Governor (Michigan) (Box 37)
      - Gun control (Box 37)
      - Health, Education and Welfare Dept (Box 37)
      - Hoffa, James (Box 37)
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 37)
      - Hunger (Box 37)
      - Immigration Service (Box 38)
      - Indians (Box 38)
      - Inflation (Box 38)
      - Interest rates (Box 38)
      - Interior Dept (Box 38)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 38)
      - Internal Revenue Service
        - General (Box 38)
        - Data Processing Center in Detroit (Box 38)
      - Job Corps (Box 38)
      - Justice Dept (Box 38)
      - Labor Dept (Box 38)
      - Lowering voting age (Box 38)
      - Michigan government (Box 38)
      - Migrant workers (Box 38)
      - Missile base (Oakland County) (Box 38)
      - Municipal taxes (Box 38)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 38)
      - National Health Insurance, 9 folders (Box 38)
      - National Institutes of Health (Box 38)
      - Nike site (Detroit) (Box 38)
      - Open Housing (Box 38)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 38)
      - Parochiaid (Box 38)
      - Patent Office (Box 38)
      - Peace Corps (Box 38)
      - Penn Central (Box 38)
      - Pollution (Box 38)
      - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box 38)
      - Public Health Service (Box 38)
      - Purdue (MWG as possible nominee for president of Purdue) (Box 38)
      - Questionnaires (Box 38)
      - Railroad Retirement Board (Box 39)
      - Resolutions (Box 39)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box 39)
      - Sex education (Box 39)
      - Selective Service reform, 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Small Business Administration (Box 39)
      - Social Security Administration (Box 39)
      - Space (Box 39)
      - State Dept (Box 39)
      - Statements (Box 39)
      - Status of women (Box 39)
      - Student unrest (Box 39)
      - Sweepstakes investigation (Box 39)
      - Supreme Court (possible MWG appointment), 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Taxes (Box 39)
      - Teamsters strike (Box 39)
      - Transportation Dept (Box 39)
      - Treasury Dept.; include Bureau of Customs, 2 folders (Box 39)
      - United Nations (Box 39)
      - United States Information Agency (Box 39)
      - University of Michigan (disruption of speech by hecklers) (Box 39)
      - Vietnam massacre (Box 39)
      - Vocational rehabilitation (Box 39)
      - Wayne State University (Box 39)
      - Welfare (Box 39)
      - Whip position (Box 39)
      - White House Conference on Children and Youth (Box 39)
      - Women-Discrimination (Box 39)
  - 92nd Congress 1971-1972
    - Legislative files
      - Agriculture (Box 40)
      - Appropriations (Box 40)
      - Armed Services (Box 40)
      - Banking and Currency (Box 40)
      - District of Columbia (Box 40)
      - Education and Labor (Box 40)
      - Foreign Affairs (Box 40)
      - Government Operations (Box 40)
      - House Administration (Box 40)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs (Box 40)
      - Internal Security (Box 40)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 40)
      - Judiciary (Box 41)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 41)
      - Post Office and Civil Service (Box 41)
      - Public Works (Box 41)
      - Rules (Box 41)
      - Science and Astronautics (Box 41)
      - Veterans Affairs (Box 41)
      - Ways and Means (Box 41)
      - Ways and Means (Box 42)
    - [Bills introduced by MWG (files not received)] (Box 42)
    - Topical Files
      - Abortion (Box 42)
      - Aid to Dependent Children (Box 42)
      - Agriculture Dept (Box 42)
      - Air and water pollution (Box 42)
      - Apter, Dr. Julia (Box 42)
      - Army (Col. Herbert charges of war crimes) (Box 42)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 42)
      - Automobile companies (Box 42)
      - Busing, 13 folders (Box 42)
      - Calley, Lt. William (Box 43)
      - Campaign, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board (Box 43)
      - Civil Service (Box 43)
      - Colleagues (communications with) (Box 43)
      - Comments and views of MWG (Box 43)
      - Commerce Dept (Box 43)
      - Committee on Committees (Box 43)
      - Conference Committee (Box 43)
      - Congressional Record inserts (Box 43)
      - Crime (Box 43)
      - Defense Dept. (Box 43)
      - Democratic National Committee (Box 43)
      - Detroit Public Health Hospital (Box 43)
      - Detroit schools (Box 43)
      - Douglas (William O.) impeachment (Box 43)
      - Drugs (Box 43)
      - Education (Box 43)
      - Electoral College Reform (Box 43)
      - Environmental pollution (Box 43)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 43)
      - Extremist groups (Box 43)
      - Family Circle article (Box 43)
      - Federal Aviation Agency (Box 43)
      - Federal Communications Commission (Box 43)
      - Federal Housing Administration (Box 43)
      - Flag desecration (Box 43)
      - Flouridation (Box 43)
      - Food and Drug Administration (Box 43)
      - Food stamp program (Box 43)
      - Foreign Policy
        - General (Box 43)
        - Cambodia (Box 43)
        - Treaties (Box 43)
        - Prisoner of war (Box 43)
        - Vietnam (Box 43)
      - Fort, Edward B (Box 43)
      - General Services Administration (Box 43)
      - Governor (Michigan) (Box 43)
      - Gridiron dinner (Box 43)
      - Griffiths (comments on television, radio, speeches, etc.) (Box 44)
      - Griffiths as possible vice presidential nominee (Box 44)
      - Gun control (Box 44)
      - Health, Education and Welfare Dept (Box 44)
      - Housing and Urban Development Dept (Box 44)
      - Indians (Box 44)
      - Insurance (Box 44)
      - Interest rates (Box 44)
      - Interior Dept (Box 44)
      - Internal Revenue Service (Box 44)
      - Labor Dept (Box 44)
      - Michigan matters (Box 44)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 44)
      - National Commission on Consumer Finance (Box 44)
      - National Health Insurance, 8 folders (Box 44)
      - National Observance Week (Box 44)
      - New Economic Policy (Box 44)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 44)
      - Pension problems (Box 45)
      - Political-district (Box 45)
      - Population (Box 45)
      - Pornography (Box 45)
      - Post Office (Box 45)
      - Postal service (Box 45)
      - Price Commission (Box 45)
      - Railroads (Box 45)
      - Resolutions (Box 45)
      - Sandler, Dr. Bernice (Box 45)
      - Sex education (Box 45)
      - Small Business Administration (Box 45)
      - Social Security Administration (Box 45)
      - SST (Box 45)
      - State Dept (Box 45)
      - State of the Union address assessment (Box 45)
      - Statements (Box 45)
      - Status of Women Committee (Box 45)
      - Subversive organizations (Box 45)
      - Supreme Court (possibility of MWG appointment) (Box 45)
      - Tariff Commission (Box 45)
      - Taxes (Box 45)
      - Transportation Dept (Box 45)
      - Treasury Dept (Box 45)
      - United Nations (Box 45)
      - Veterans Administration
        - General (Box 45)
        - Hospitals (Box 45)
      - Vicary, Tice (Box 45)
      - Wage and Price controls, 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Women
        - Civil service (Box 45)
        - Equal Rights Amendment, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Organizations (Box 45)
        - State legislators (Box 45)
  - 93rd Congress 1973-1974
    - Legislative files
      - Agriculture (Box 46)
      - Appropriations (Box 46)
      - Armed Services (Box 46)
      - Banking and Currency (Box 46)
      - District of Columbia (Box 46)
      - Education and Labor (Box 46)
      - Foreign Affairs (Box 46)
      - Government Operations (Box 47)
      - House Administration (Box 47)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs (Box 47)
      - International and Foreign Commerce (Box 47)
      - Judiciary (Box 47)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 47)
      - Post Office and Civil Service (Box 47)
      - Public Works (Box 47)
      - Public Works (Box 48)
      - Rules (Box 48)
      - Science and Astronautics (Box 48)
      - Select Committee on Committees (Box 48)
      - Standards of Official Conduct (Box 48)
      - Veterans Affairs (Box 48)
      - Ways and Means (Box 48)
      - Ways and Means (Box 49)
      - Ways and Means (Box 50)
      - Joint Economic Committee
        - General (Box 50)
        - Subcommittee on Fiscal Policy (Box 50)
          include files concerning hearings on economic problems of women
    - Bills introduced by MWG (Box 51)
    - Bills introduced by MWG (Box 52)
    - Bills introduced by MWG (Box 53)
    - Topical Files
      - Abortion, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Agnew, Spiro T (Box 53)
      - Agriculture Dept., 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Air and Water Pollution (Box 53)
      - Air Force Beagles (Box 53)
      - Amnesty (Box 53)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 53)
      - Automobile companies (Box 53)
      - Automobile safety (Box 53)
      - Bicentennial (Box 53)
      - Budget (Box 53)
      - Busing, 7 folders (Box 53)
      - Campaign issues (Box 54)
      - Capital punishment (Box 54)
      - Civil Rights (Box 54)
      - Civil Service Commission (Box 54)
      - Colleagues (communications with) (Box 54)
      - Comments and Views of MWG (Box 54)
      - Commerce Dept (Box 54)
      - Committee on Committees (Box 54)
      - Committee memberships (Box 54)
      - Congressional Record inserts (Box 54)
      - Consumer legislation (Box 54)
      - Contests (include Woman of Conscience) (Box 54)
      - Cox, Arlene (Box 54)
      - Crime (Box 54)
      - Day Care (Box 54)
      - Defense Dept. (Box 54)
      - Democratic Advisory Council of Elected Officials (Box 54)
      - Democratic National Committee (Box 54)
      - Detroit
        - General (Box 54)
        - Detroit Schools, 3 folders (Box 54)
        - Detroit teachers' strike (Box 54)
      - Donnelly, Elaine (Box 54)
      - Drugs (Box 54)
      - Education (Box 54)
      - Electoral College reform (Box 54)
      - Energy
        - Air pollution (Box 54)
        - Oil companies (Box 54)
        - Rationing (Box 54)
      - Energy crisis (Box 54)
      - Environmental pollution (Box 54)
      - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 54)
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 54)
      - Federal Communications Commission (Box 54)
      - Federal Deposit Insurance Commission (Box 54)
      - Federal Home Loan Bank Board (Box 54)
      - Federal pay raise (Box 54)
      - Federal Power Commission (Box 54)
      - Federal Trade Commission (Box 54)
      - Flags (Box 54)
      - Food and Drug Administration
        - General (Box 54)
        - Vitamins (Box 54)
      - Food Stamp program (Box 54)
      - Ford, Gerald R (Box 54)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 54)
      - Foreign Policy
        - General (Box 54)
        - Cambodia (Box 54)
        - Cyprus (Box 55)
        - Middle East, 4 folders (Box 55)
        - Treaties (Box 55)
        - U.S.S.R (Box 55)
        - Vietnam (Box 55)
        - Vietnam prisoners of war (Box 55)
      - Government spending (Box 55)
      - Griffiths, Martha
        - Endorsements (Box 55)
        - Mike Douglas Show (Box 55)
        - Retirement (Box 55)
        - Television and radio speeches (Box 55)
        - Today Show appearance regarding the ERA (Box 55)
        - Woman of the Year (Box 55)
      - Gun control (Box 55)
      - Health, Education and Welfare Dept
        - General (Box 55)
        - Nursing home standards (Box 55)
      - Hijacking (Box 55)
      - Homestead tax exemption (Box 55)
      - Housing and Urban Development Dept
        - General (Box 55)
        - Detroit problem (Box 55)
      - Impeachment of President Nixon, 6 folders (Box 55)
      - Impoundment (Box 56)
      - Indians (Box 56)
      - Indritz, Phineas (Box 56)
      - Inflation (Box 56)
      - Insurance (Box 56)
      - Interior Dept (Box 56)
      - Internal Revenue Service (Box 56)
      - Interstate Commerce Dept (Box 56)
      - Justice Dept (Box 56)
      - Labor Dept (Box 56)
      - Leadership (Box 56)
      - Lowering the voting age (Box 56)
      - Michigan Legislature (Box 56)
      - Michigan (State) (Box 56)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 56)
      - National Commission on Consumer Finance (Box 56)
      - National Health Insurance, 12 folders (Box 56)
      - Nixon pardon (Box 56)
      - Nixon resignation (Box 56)
      - Open housing (Box 56)
      - Pensions-Women (Box 56)
      - Population (Box 56)
      - Post Office (obscene mail and pornography) (Box 56)
      - Poverty (Box 56)
      - Presidential immunity (Box 56)
      - Probate Court reform (Box 56)
      - Property tax (Box 56)
      - Quello, James (Box 57)
      - Questionnaires (Box 57)
      - Railroad Retirement Board (Box 57)
      - Railroads (Box 57)
      - Rawalt, Marguerite (Box 57)
      - Resolutions (Box 57)
      - School Lunch Program (Box 57)
      - Selective Service-draft reform (Box 57)
      - Senior citizens (Box 57)
      - Seventeenth Congressional District
        - Democratic Party (Box 57)
        - Election (Box 57)
      - Sex education (Box 57)
      - Small Business Administration (Box 57)
      - Social Security Administration (Box 57)
      - Space (Box 57)
      - Special Prosecutor (Box 57)
      - SST (Box 57)
      - State Dept (Box 57)
      - State taxation (Box 57)
      - Statements (Box 57)
      - Strikes (Box 57)
      - Student unrest (Box 57)
      - Supreme Court (Box 57)
      - Taxes (Box 57)
      - Transition request (expenses for President Nixon) (Box 57)
      - Transportation Dept (Box 57)
      - Treasury Dept
        - General (Box 57)
        - Revenue sharing (Box 57)
      - United Nations (Box 57)
      - United Service Organizations (Box 57)
      - Veterans Administration (Box 57)
      - Veterans (Private Edward Slovik) (Box 57)
      - Vicary, Tice (Box 57)
      - Vice President (choice of Nelson Rockefeller) (Box 57)
      - Wage-price controls (Box 57)
      - Watergate (Box 57)
      - Welfare (Box 57)
      - Women (Box 57)
- Schedules
  - 1960-1974 (Box 58)
    (some gaps)
- Sound recordings
  - Reel-to-reel and cassettes
    - "Report on Congress" (weekly report of MWG) circa 1955-1956, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Box 59)
      (This tape consists of a number of reports probably all recorded at one time.)
    - Recording of MWG discussing the Federal National Mortgage Association, family food budgets, consent decrees in anti-trust suits, the Statistical Abstract of the United States, and population growth and new states., circa 1957, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Box 59)
    - Radio report of MWG discussing the achievements of the 85th Congress. October-November 1957, 4 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 59)
    - "Report from Washington" on the topic of civil defense system. October 20, 1957, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 59)
    - Recording of "Congress in Action" featuring MWG discussing the extension of the Reciprocal Trade Agreements Act with guest Henry Kerns. February 20, 1958, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. 13:08 (Box 59)
    - Recording of interview between MWG and Rajni Kaul of the Voice of America on Griffith's entry into politics, issues before the Congress, and life as member of Congress. May 15, 1958, 1 audiotapes 15 min.; reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Box 59)
    - Recording discussing function of the General Accounting Office. circa 1959, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 3 in. (Box 59)
    - Interview with MWG on the trade expansion act recorded for the Voice of America. March 15, 1962, 1 audiotapes 4 min.; reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Box 59)
    - Recording of interview with MWG conducted by Ray Courage on tax cut bill in Congress. circa 1963, 1 audiotapes 12 min.; reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 59)
    - Recording of ceremonies in capitol rotunda for President John F. Kennedy. Participants include: Russell Black, Mike Mansfield, Earl Warren, and John McCormack. November 24, 1963, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Box 59)
    - Recording of Congressman Peter Dupont of Delaware with guest MWG discussing economic discrimination of women. circa 1970, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. 5:05 (Box 59)
    - Recordings of statement made for program "Capitol Hill Today;" include brief comments on sex discrimination October 21, 1969, August 10, 1970 and health service, February 10, 1970, 3 audiotapes each statement runs about 30 seconds; reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 3 in. (Box 59)
    - Radio recording of "What's the Issue?" on the subject of welfare with guest Representative Martha Griffiths. Host: Arch N. Booth; Report: Craig Palmer. April 12, 1973, 1 audiotapes 20:5; reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Box 59)
    - Recording of panel discussion at the Associated Credit Bureaus Conference on the topic, "Sex discrimination in credit granting." Panelists include: MWG, Milton Shovert?, Charles F. Hayward. May 10, 1973, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Recording of "Foundation Forum," information service of the National Foundation of Health, Welfare and Pension Plans, Inc., featuring in part MWG discussing her national health care bill. May 1973, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Recording of interview with MWG conducted by Robert Barrie of the United Mine Workers on the subject of National Health Insurance. May 9, 1974, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      poor sound quality
    - Recording of speech of MWG before the National Convention of the Business and Professional Women's Clubs on the subject of the Equal Rights Amendment. July 22, 1974, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Recordings of interviews with MWG conducted by Sister Emily George as part of her research for a biography of Congresswoman Griffiths. 1977-1978, 23 audiocassettes (Box 59)
  - Phonograph Records